Operations to perform:
  Apply all migrations: admin, assets, attendance, auth, cold_campaign, compliance, contenttypes, core, employees, engagement, expenses, helpdesk, leave, notifications, offboarding, onboarding, organization, payroll, performance, recruitment, sessions, shifts, token_blacklist, wfh
Running pre-migrate handlers for application admin
Running pre-migrate handlers for application auth
Running pre-migrate handlers for application contenttypes
Running pre-migrate handlers for application sessions
Running pre-migrate handlers for application rest_framework_simplejwt
Running pre-migrate handlers for application token_blacklist
Running pre-migrate handlers for application simple_history
Running pre-migrate handlers for application core
Running pre-migrate handlers for application organization
Running pre-migrate handlers for application employees
Running pre-migrate handlers for application attendance
Running pre-migrate handlers for application leave
Running pre-migrate handlers for application shifts
Running pre-migrate handlers for application payroll
Running pre-migrate handlers for application compliance
Running pre-migrate handlers for application notifications
Running pre-migrate handlers for application recruitment
Running pre-migrate handlers for application wfh
Running pre-migrate handlers for application onboarding
Running pre-migrate handlers for application expenses
Running pre-migrate handlers for application assets
Running pre-migrate handlers for application helpdesk
Running pre-migrate handlers for application performance
Running pre-migrate handlers for application engagement
Running pre-migrate handlers for application offboarding
Running pre-migrate handlers for application cold_campaign
Running migrations:
  Applying core.0013_tenant_jurisdiction_fields... OK (0.328s)
  Applying organization.0004_legalentity... OK (0.172s)
  Applying employees.0003_jurisdiction_tax_profile... OK (0.219s)
  Applying compliance.0001_initial... OK (0.156s)
  Applying payroll.0002_jurisdiction_models... OK (1.203s)
Running post-migrate handlers for application admin
Running post-migrate handlers for application auth
Running post-migrate handlers for application contenttypes
Running post-migrate handlers for application sessions
Running post-migrate handlers for application rest_framework_simplejwt
Running post-migrate handlers for application token_blacklist
Running post-migrate handlers for application simple_history
Running post-migrate handlers for application core
Running post-migrate handlers for application organization
Adding content type 'organization | legalentity'
Adding permission 'Permission object (417)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (418)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (419)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (420)'
Running post-migrate handlers for application employees
Adding content type 'employees | employeetaxprofile'
Adding permission 'Permission object (421)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (422)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (423)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (424)'
Running post-migrate handlers for application attendance
Running post-migrate handlers for application leave
Running post-migrate handlers for application shifts
Running post-migrate handlers for application payroll
Adding content type 'payroll | payrolllineitem'
Adding content type 'payroll | taxdeclaration'
Adding permission 'Permission object (425)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (426)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (427)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (428)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (429)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (430)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (431)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (432)'
Running post-migrate handlers for application compliance
Adding content type 'compliance | compliancedocument'
Adding content type 'compliance | filingrecord'
Adding content type 'compliance | statutoryruleset'
Adding permission 'Permission object (433)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (434)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (435)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (436)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (437)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (438)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (439)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (440)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (441)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (442)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (443)'
Adding permission 'Permission object (444)'
Running post-migrate handlers for application notifications
Running post-migrate handlers for application recruitment
Running post-migrate handlers for application wfh
Running post-migrate handlers for application onboarding
Running post-migrate handlers for application expenses
Running post-migrate handlers for application assets
Running post-migrate handlers for application helpdesk
Running post-migrate handlers for application performance
Running post-migrate handlers for application engagement
Running post-migrate handlers for application offboarding
Running post-migrate handlers for application cold_campaign
